Illinois Central Gulf Railroad Miscellany 5197
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Alabama and Vicksburg Railway-Rates of Pay and Rules for various crafts, 1898-1946 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Rules and Regulations, 1925; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 6)
    The Alabama and Vicksburg Railway-Rules and Regulations concerning Locomotive Firemen, Hostlers and Helpers
  - Item 6: Rates of Pay, 1917; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Rates of Pay, 1901; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Alabama and Vicksburg Railway-Rates of Pay and other Regulations concerning Locomotive Engineers
  - Item 8: Rates of Pay, 1912; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Rates of Pay, 1924; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 6)
    The Alabama and Vicksburg Railway-Rates of Pay and other Regulations concerning Locomotive Firemen, Hostlers and Helpers
  - Item 10: Rates of Pay, 1937; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 6)
    The Alabama and Vicksburg Railway-Rates of Pay and other Regulations concerning Conductors
  - Item 11: Rates of Pay, 1898; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Alabama and Vicksburg Railway-Rates of Pay and other Regulations concerning Engineers
  - Item 12: Rates of Pay, 1911; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Rates of Pay, 1901; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Rates of Pay, 1902; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: Rates of Pay, 1906; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: Rates of Pay, 1906; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 17: Rates of Pay, 1906; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: Rates of Pay, 1909; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 19: Rates of Pay, 1909; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 20: Rates of Pay, 1909; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 21: Rates of Pay, 1910; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Alabama and Vicksburg Railway-Rates of Pay and other Regulations concerning Conductors, White Trainmen and White Yardmen
  - Item 22: Rates of Pay, 1910; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 23: Rates of Pay, 1912; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Alabama and Vicksburg Railway-Rates of Pay and other Regulations concerning Trainmen and Yardmen
- Various subsidiary railroads-Rules, Rates of Pay, Agreements, 1901-1946 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Instructions for Student Locomotive Firemen, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Illinois Central System- Instructions for Student Locomotive Firemen
  - Item 2: Dispatch Freight System, 1925; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., The Yazoo and Mississippi Valley Railroad Co., and Gulf and Ship Island Railroad Co.- Dispatch Freight System
  - Item 3: Agreement between MCRC and the Conductors, Trainmen and Yardmen, 1946; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Agreement between Mississippi Central Railroad Company and the Conductors, Trainmen and Yardmen, represented by the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen
  - Item 4: Pension System of Missouri Pacific Lines, 1926; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Missouri Pacific Lines- Pension System of Missouri Pacific Lines, adopted by the Boards of Directors
  - Item 5: Pass Rules, 1901; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Instructions Governing Free Travel and Passes
  - Item 6: Schedule of Rules, Regulations, and Rates of Pay, 1919; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 7)
    United States Railroad Administration, Schedule of Rules, Regulations, and Rates of Pay
  - Item 7: Schedule of Wages, 1918; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 7)
    United States Railroad Administration and Illinois Central Railroad, Schedule of Wages of Locomotive Firemen
  - Item 8: Maintenance of Brake and Train Air Signal Equipment, 1926; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 7)
    American Railway Association-Maintenance of Brake and Train Air Signal Equipment, adopted as Standard 1925
  - Item 9: Schedule of Wages and Rules, 1925; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Gulf and Ship island Railroad Co., Schedule of Wages and Rules for Trainmen in Passenger, Freight and Yard Service
  - Item 10: Schedule of Rules, Regulations and Rates of Pay, 1923; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Gulf and Ship Island Railroad Co., Schedule of Rules, Regulations and Rates of Pay for Trainmen and Yardmen
  - Item 11: Schedule of Rules, Regulations and Rates of Pay, 1924; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Gulf and Ship Island Railroad Co., Schedule of Rules, Regulations and Rates of Pay for Conductors
  - Item 12: Schedule of Rules, Regulations and Rates of Pay, 1924; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: Schedule of Rules, Regulations and Rates of Pay, 1941; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Gulf and Ship Island Railroad Co., Schedule of Rules, Regulations and Rates of Pay for Locomotive Engineers, Firemen and Hostlers
  - Item 14: Rules for the Operation of Trains, 1929; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Paducah and Illinois Railroad Co., Rules for the Operation of Trains by Centralized Control Signal System
- Illinois Central Railroad Company-Rules, Agreements, and Schedules of Wages of various crafts, 1891-1933 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Agreements in Effect, 1926; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Illinois Central Railroad Company- Agreements in Effect between the Illinois Central Railroad and Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, also Interpretations by General Chairmen
  - Item 2: Schedule of Wages of Locomotive Firemen, 1902; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Illinois Central Railroad Company- Schedule of Wages of Locomotive Firemen
  - Item 3: Schedule of Wages of Locomotive Engineers, 1933; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Illinois Central Railroad Company- Schedule of Wages of Locomotive Engineers
  - Item 4: Rules of the Transportation Department, 1891; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Rules of the Transportation Department
  - Item 5: Schedule of Wages of Locomotive Engineers, 1917; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Schedule of Wages of Locomotive Engineers
  - Item 6: Schedule of Wages of for Conductors, 1924; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Schedule of Wages of for Conductors
  - Item 7: Rules of the Road Department, 1895; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Rules of the Road Department
  - Item 8: Rules and Instructions for the Government of the Employes, 1891; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Rules and Instructions for the Government of the Employes of the Road Department
- Illinois Central Railroad Company-Rules, Agreements, and Schedules of Wages of various crafts, 1898-1941 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Rules and Rates of Pay, 1936; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Company-Rules and Rates of Pay for Trainmen
  - Item 2: Schedule of Wages, 1938; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Schedule of Wages, 1903; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Company- Schedule of Wages for Trainmen in Suburban Passenger Service
  - Item 4: Schedule of Wages, 1907; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Schedule of Wages, 1913; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Schedule of Wages, 1903; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Schedule of Rules and Rates of Pay, 1920; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Company- Schedule of Rules and Rates of Pay for Trainmen
  - Item 8: Schedule of Wages and Rules, 1898; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Company- Schedule of Wages and Rules of Employment for the Trainmen in Passenger and Freight Service on the Illinois Railroad
  - Item 9: Schedule of Wages, 1903; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Schedule of Wages, 1912; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Schedule of Wages, 1903; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Company- Schedule of Wages for Switching Service/Switchmen
  - Item 12: Rates of Pay, 1907; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Company- Rates of Pay for Engineers
  - Item 13: Rules for the Maintenance of Way and Structures, 1925; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., The Yazoo and Mississippi Valley Railroad Co., Gulf and Ship Island Railroad Co., Rules for the Maintenance of Way and Structures
  - Item 14: Schedule of Wages, 1922; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co.- Schedule of Wages of Locomotive Engineers
  - Item 15: Schedule of Wages and Rules, 1920; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co.- Schedule of Wages and Rules for Conductors
  - Item 16: Schedule of Wages, 1903; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co.- Schedule of Wages of Locomotive Enginemen
- Yazoo and Mississippi Valley Railroad-Schedules of wages and Rules for various crafts, 1895-1943 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Schedule of Wages, 1923; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 3)
    The Yazoo and Mississippi Valley Railroad-Schedule of Wages of Locomotive Engineers
  - Item 2: Schedule of Wages, 1938; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 3)
    The Yazoo and Mississippi Valley Railroad-Schedule of Wages of Locomotive Firemen
  - Item 3: Rules and Regulations, 1943; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 3)
    The Yazoo and Mississippi Valley Railroad- Rules and Regulations concerning Locomotive Firemen, Hostlers and Helpers
  - Item 4: Schedule of Wages, 1912; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 3)
    The Yazoo and Mississippi Valley Railroad- Schedule of Wages for Trainmen in Passenger and Freight Service
  - Item 5: Schedule of Wages, 1910; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 3)
    The Yazoo and Mississippi Valley Railroad- Schedule of Wages for Switching Service at Points Named
  - Item 6: Schedule of Wages, 1912; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 3)
    The Yazoo and Mississippi Valley Railroad- Schedule of Wages of Locomotive Engineers
  - Item 7: Schedule of Wages, 1913; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Schedule of Wages, 1914; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Schedule of Wages, 1915; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Schedule of Wages, 1925; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 3)
    The Yazoo and Mississippi Valley Railroad- Schedule of Wages of Locomotive Firemen
  - Item 11: Schedule of Wages and Rules, 1924; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 3)
    The Yazoo and Mississippi Valley Railroad- Schedule of Wages and Rules governing Yardmen and Switchtenders
  - Item 12: Schedule of Wages and Rules, 1924; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 3)
    The Yazoo and Mississippi Valley Railroad- Schedule of Wages and rules for Trainmen
  - Item 13: Schedule of Wages and Rules, 1924; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 3)
    The Yazoo and Mississippi Valley Railroad- Schedule of Wages and Rules for Conductors
  - Item 14: Rules of the Road Dept., 1895; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 3)
    The Yazoo and Mississippi Valley Railroad- Rules of the Road Department
  - Item 15: Schedule of Wages, 1917; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: Schedule of Wages, 1918; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: Schedule of Wages and Rules, 1920; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 3)
    The Yazoo and Mississippi Valley Railroad- Schedule of Wages and Rules for Trainmen
  - Item 18: Schedule of Wages and Rules, 1937; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: Schedule of Wages, 1925; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 20: Schedule of Wages, 1937; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 21: Schedule of Wages, 1907; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 22: Schedule of Wages, 1920; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 23: Schedule of Wages and Rules, 1920; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 24: Schedule of Wages and Rules, 1920; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Slater's Telegraphic Code, Sixth Edition, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Slater's Telegraphic Code to Ensure the Secresy in the Transmission of Telegrams, Sixth Edition
- United States Railroad Admin.-Rules and Instructions for ICRR, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Rules and Instructions, 1919; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 5)
    United States Railroad Admin.-Rules and Instructions for the Maintenance of Way and Structures
  - Item 2: Schedule of Wages, 1919; Pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 5)
    United States Railroad Admin.- Schedule of Wages of Locomotive Firemen
- Labor Management Committee Reports, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 1a)
  April 23,1971
  - Item 1: Report of Task Force I, 1971; Pamphlet (Box 6, Folder 1a)
    Decade of Decision Terminals- Report of Task Force I to the Labor and Management Committee
  - Item 2: A Report on Railroad Track and Roadway, 1971; Pamphlet (Box 6, Folder 1a)
    Decade of Decision- A Report on Railroad Track and Roadway, Task Force II Labor and Management Committee
- ICRR Employee Bulletins, 1968-1973 and ICRR Sample Check (Box 6, Folder 1b)
- ICRR and various subsidiary railroads-Rules, Rates of Pay, Agreements, 1890-1937 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- ICRRs-Rules, Rates of Pay, Agreements, 1890-1937 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Master Car Builder's Association-Code of Rules, 1893-1917 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  1893, 1915, 1916, 1917
  - Item 1: Code of Rules, 1893; Pamphlet (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Master Car Builders' Association- Code of Rules governing the Condition of, and Repairs to, Freight Cars
  - Item 2: Interpretations of the Rules of Interchange, 1915; Pamphlet (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Master Car Builders' Association- Circular. No 6: Interpretations of the Rules of Interchange
  - Item 3: Interpretations of the Rules of Interchange, 1916; Pamphlet (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Master Car Builders' Association- Circular. No 11: For the Arbitration Committee- Interpretations of the Rules of Interchange
  - Item 4: Code of Rules, 1917; Pamphlet (Box 6, Folder 4)
- New Interchange Association and Master Car Builder's Association-Code of Rules, 1886 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Combination of items that exempt car-owners from responsibility
- Illinois Central Railroad Company-Schedule of Wages, 1900-1901 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Illinois Central Service-Gold Pass Luncheon pamphlet [folder 1 of 2], 1941-1959 (Box 6, Folder 7a)
  1941, 1944, 1945, 1951-1953, 1955-1957, 1959
  - Item 1: Gold Pass Luncheon, 1941; Pamphlet (Box 6, Folder 7a)
    Illinois Central Service- Luncheon honoring the 1941 Group of 50-Year Veterans of Illinoi Central Service
  - Item 2: Gold Pass Luncheon, 1944; Pamphlet (Box 6, Folder 7a)
    Illinois Central Service- Luncheon Honoring the 1944 Group of 50-Year Veterans of Illinois Central Service
  - Item 3: Gold Pass Luncheon, 1945; Pamphlet (Box 6, Folder 7a)
    Illinois Central Service- Luncheon Honoring the 1945 Group of 50-Year Veterans of Illinois Central Service
  - Item 4: Gold Pass Luncheon, 1945; Pamphlet (Box 6, Folder 7a)
  - Item 5: Gold Pass Luncheon, 1959; Pamphlet (Box 6, Folder 7a)
    Gold Pass Luncheon honoring the 1959 Group of 50-Year Veterans of Illinois Central Service
  - Item 6: Gold Pass Luncheon, 1953; Pamphlet (Box 6, Folder 7a)
    Illinois Central Service- Luncheon Honoring the 1953 Group of 50-Year Veterans of Illinois Central Service
  - Item 7: Gold Pass Luncheon, 1952; Pamphlet (Box 6, Folder 7a)
    Illinois Central Service- Luncheon Honoring the 1952 Group of 50-Year Veterans of Illinois Central Service
  - Item 8: Gold Pass Luncheon, 1951; Pamphlet (Box 6, Folder 7a)
    Illinois Central Service- Luncheon Honoring the 1951 Group of 50-Year Veterans of Illinois Central Service
  - Item 9: Gold Pass Luncheon, 1955; Pamphlet (Box 6, Folder 7a)
    Illinois Central Service- Luncheon Honoring the 1955 Group of 50-Year Veterans of Illinois Central Service
  - Item 10: Gold Pass Luncheon, 1956; Pamphlet (Box 6, Folder 7a)
    Illinois Central Service- Luncheon Honoring the 1956 Group of 50-Year Veterans of Illinois Central Service
  - Item 11: Gold Pass Luncheon, 1957; Pamphlet (Box 6, Folder 7a)
    Illinois Central Service- Luncheon Honoring the 1957 Group of 50-Year Veterans of Illinois Central Service
- Illinois Central Service-Gold Pass Luncheon pamphlet [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1966 (Box 6, Folder 7b)
  - Item 1: Gold Pass Luncheon, 1964; Pamphlet (Box 6, Folder 7b)
    Illinois Central Service- Luncheon Honoring the 1964 Group of 50-Year Veterans of Illinois Central Service
  - Item 2: Gold Pass Luncheon, 1965; Pamphlet (Box 6, Folder 7b)
    Illinois Central Service- Luncheon Honoring the 1965 Group of 50-Year Veterans of Illinois Central Service
  - Item 3: Gold Pass Luncheon, 1966; Pamphlet (Box 6, Folder 7b)
    Illinois Central Service- Luncheon Honoring the 1966 Group of 50-Year Veterans of Illinois Central Service
  - Item 4: Gold Pass Luncheon, 1960; Pamphlet (Box 6, Folder 7b)
    Illinois Central Service- Luncheon Honoring the 1960 Group of 50-Year Veterans of Illinois Central Service
  - Item 5: Gold Pass Luncheon, 1961; Pamphlet (Box 6, Folder 7b)
    Illinois Central Service- Luncheon Honoring the 1961 Group of 50-Year Veterans of Illinois Central Service
  - Item 6: Gold Pass Luncheon, 1962; Pamphlet (Box 6, Folder 7b)
    Illinois Central Service- Luncheon Honoring the 1962 Group of 50-Year Veterans of Illinois Central Service
  - Item 7: Gold Pass Luncheon, 1963; Pamphlet (Box 6, Folder 7b)
    Illinois Central Service- Luncheon Honoring the 1963 Group of 50-Year Veterans of Illinois Central Service